question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
